<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="44"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Chapter01
Chapter02
Chapter03
Chapter04
Chapter05
Chapter06
3
4 Shaping a Prime Environment, Putting the Economy into Gear
An Industrial Economy Stronghold in Tainan
Investing in Tainan for Double Advantage
Monthly Investment Conferences, Speedy Efficiency
Upgrading Smart Living, Creating a Nice Place to Live
Comfortably Warm Climate Convenient Transportation in Tainan Smart City
Twin Engines: Tainan’s Green Energy Hub and Science Park Clusters
Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City Southern Taiwan Science Park Industry Clusters
Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
Tainan’s 14 Bedrock Industries
Cultural Knowledge and Digital Content Industries High-Value Materials Know-how
Biomedical Technology
Diverse Industrial Park Development,
Pooling Abundant Energy
Support and Services
8
12
18
26 for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
Easy-to-Apply-for Funding Sources
A Set of Supports for R&D
Tourism Factories – A Strong Boost for Local Vitalization
Combining Public and Private Resources, 34 Reaching out to the World
Tainan’s Convention and Exhibition Spotlights
Industries Go International, Businesses Expand Domains Contact Window
]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 2
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
Total population
1.88million
(7th highest in Taiwan)
Land area
2,191 square kilometers (6th largest in Taiwan)
Advanced 5 nm and 3 nm manufacturing processes in the Southern Taiwan Science Park
With investments totaling around NT$1.15 trillion, the park has driven the creation of some
72,000 jobs in semiconductor related equipment, materials, support and service industries.
Tainan is rated by Greenpeace as having the overall best sustainable
energy performance of Taiwan’s
six special municipalities.
Tainan’s 14 large industry clusters are the most numerous and most complete in all of Taiwan.
]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ An Industrial Economy
Stronghold in Tainan
Tainan, the historic gateway to Taiwan, is renowned for its long and rich cultural heritage. It is also blessed with a very pleasant climate, with a lot of sunshine and little rain, the sun shining for an average of close to six hours a day all year round. Under these favorable climatic conditions, it has successfully developed a green energy technology industry, focusing mainly on solar power, for responding to global climate change. The city has Taiwan’s most concentrated solar industry cluster, with strong R&D and innovation capabilities and abundant production experience. It also has all kinds of other high-quality industry clusters, making it an ideal choice of location as an Asian green energy innovation center and operations headquarters, able to help investors speedily penetrate emerging markets in the Asia-Pacific region.
Investors who choose to invest in Tainan can obtain many kinds of premium support from our city government’s investment promotion measures. Plus, Tainan’s historical development and geographic location have endowed it with a rich variety of cultural adornments and architectural features, which have been developed into unique business districts beguiling visitors with a splendid array of fine goods and delicious cuisines. Furthermore, Tainan leads the whole of Taiwan in demonstrating the adoption of smart city technologies. With its smart parking meters, demonstration site for the driverless cars of the future, and convenient urban infrastructure, alongside its increasingly local and at the same time increasingly international cultural power, Tainan is primed for charging into international markets and mastering the future.
22
tourism factories.
3
]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                  HAPTER C1
Investing in Tainan for Double Advantage
To boost national development, the central government launched a plan to actively promote five key innovative industries, including the green energy industry. Securing a prominent role in this industry, Tainan has made big strides in incorporating smart technology, green energy, circular economy and water-friendly design into infrastructure and buildings, becoming one of the Asia-Pacific region’s foremost demonstration sites for green energy technologies, fostering new types of community, and promoting forward- looking industries.
     4
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="7" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Monthly Investment Conferences, Speedy Efficiency
Tainan City Government has specially instituted monthly investment conferences, convened by the mayor, to promote and facilitate investment. Through these meetings, and by providing investors with expert, customized assistance from dedicated case managers, the city administration is pushing hard to adjust the city’s industrial structure and create the driving forces for the city’s next wave of economic growth.
Tainan is pulling out all the stops to help overseas Taiwanese businesses bring investment back to Taiwan. It has set up a single window service for business registration, with provision for online applications, mobile payment, and diverse information systems enabling easy public inquiry, to construct a positive and efficient investment environment, and create visible future prospects for young people.
Specific Dedicated Project-oriented responsibilities case managers
Shaping a Prime Environment, Getting the Economy into Gear
To spur the momentum of investment in Tainan, the city government is pushing on with regulatory loosening, eliminating investment barriers, and creating a prime investment environment. In addition to speeding up public infrastructure building, it is also working actively to solve problems encountered by investors re land, labor, water, power and specialist talent, and opening up bottlenecks in industrial operations, to boost investor confidence and vitalize overall economic growth.
                         Hastening
the return
of Taiwanese enterprises from overseas
Collaboration between central and local government
Oriented to manufacturers’ needs
One-stop window, with mobile service
Tainan City Government employs five main strategies and methods to speedily help enterprises solve problems re insufficiency of water, power, labor, land and talent.
Proactively scouting out investment interest
       5
  Investing in Tainan for Double Advantage
   ]]></page><page Index="8" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   Solarized dormitories
   Green factories Rooftop solar panels
Large agricultural greenhouses
Solarized communities
                                   Five major solarized roofs
Five major ground-based PV arrays
Landfills
             Solarized communities
Waterside spaces
Green facilities
Land for green energy use
             Sustainable Development of Water Resources
Tainan City Government is taking a multi-pronged approach to ensuring an adequate water supply to meet long-term demand. This consists of measures for augmenting water sources through water reclamation; for renewing and improving reservoir and piping facilities to reduce water leakage; for adjusting water distribution by installing additional pipe connections; and for bolstering backup capacity to enhance the water supply system.
Active Development of Energy Sources for Power Supply
Tainan has a sound and complete electric power system. To make the most of Tainan’s climatic and geographic advantages, the city government has expanded implementation of the Solar City of Tainan Project 2.0, promoting the installation of five large PV arrays on rooftops and five large PV arrays on the ground, to increase the prevalence of solar power utilization in the city. This will help advance making Taiwan into a nuclear-free homeland and bringing on the age of the green economy. Besides boosting investor confidence, our development of stable and clean energy sources will assist our gathering in of talent for emerging industries and luring in of foreign business investors.
   The excellent results of our Solar City Project have gained much approbation. In addition to three successive years of being rated by the Energy Bureau of the Ministry of Economic Affairs as a city or county with outstanding achievement in promoting renewable energy, Tainan also won a gold award in the APEC Energy Smart Communities Initiative (ESCI) Best Practices Awards Program. This performance has helped attract investment in Tainan by big-name international corporations such as Google and Tokyo Electric Power Company.
• Evaluated by Greenpeace as the best of Taiwan’s six special municipalities for Renewable Energy Governance Performance.
• Awarded gold as a Low Carbon Model Town in APEC’s 2017 Energy Smart Communities Initiative (ESCI) Best Practices Awards Program.
• Selected by Google for the siting of its first renewable energy project in Asia, and also for investment in establishing a data center.
 6 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
  ]]></page><page Index="9" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Nurturing high-grade talent
Tainan is home to a strong, proficient workforce and a quality talent pool, thanks to the presence of top-notch schools and colleges throughout the city. There are 332 schools of all levels in Tainan, including 15 colleges and universities. These campuses produce more than 100,000 capable graduates every year. According to the World Economic Forum’s ranking for labor market efficiency in the 2017-2018 Global Competitiveness Report, Taiwan placed 25th out of the 137 countries evaluated.
Under the National Strategic Plan for Regional Revitalization, local consensus on revitalization vision is gathered through a bottom-up approach. Then, local talent to meet that vision is unearthed and nurtured under Tainan’s Innovation and Creativity Plan. With the major research bodies that have moved into Tainan, including Academia Sinica, the Industrial Technology Research Institute, the National Center for Research on Earthquake Engineering, the World Vegetable Center, the National Health Research Institutes, and the Food Industry Research and Development Institute, the city’s recruitment of elite R&D talent can amply supply the talent needed by multinational enterprises for penetrating Asia-Pacific markets.
Excellent Land Resources
The City of Tainan occupies an area of 2,191.7 square kilometers, backed by mountains and facing the sea. Sitting in the heart of Taiwan’s biggest plain, with the geographic advantage of an expansive hinterland, it has developed rapidly from a typical agricultural county and city into a major industrial city with more than 9,000 factories. And in recent years, as high-tech industries and R&D units have moved in, Tainan has gradually transformed into a high-tech city.
   7
Investing in Tainan for Double Advantage
 ]]></page><page Index="10" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                           HAPTER C2
Upgrading Smart Living, Creating a
Nice Place to Live
            Located in the southwest of Taiwan, at the center of the Chianan Plain, Tainan occupies mostly gentle terrain, criss-crossed by rivers large and small, rising into hills and mountains in the east. Divided into 37 districts, this former capital’s greatest asset and feature is its rich endowment of culture. By revitalizing its heritage sites and developing tourism facilities, it has come to play a major role in showcasing Taiwan culture.
       8
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="11" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   Comfortably Warm Climate
Tainan City is located south of the Tropic of Cancer, its eastern border in the foothills of the Central Mountain Range, and fronted by the Taiwan Strait in the west. It is subtropical, with a mild climate and abundant agricultural products, mainly rice, sugar cane, and miscellaneous grain crops, plus numerous local specialties. It has Taiwan’s largest areas of paddy fields, dry fields, fish farms, salt fields, lotus ponds and water chestnut plantations. Its geographic and climatic conditions spawned a coastal salt production industry with a history of more than 300 years. With its rich cultural and geologic diversity, anyone who visits Tainan, whether for tourism, a business trip, or a long- term stay, can deeply feel the city’s alluring charm.
                                                    Nanjing Hangzhou
Xiamen Hong Kong
Bangkok
Manila
Shanghai
Seoul
Tokyo
                               Tainan
Setting sights globally, first choice Tainan
                                   Convenient Transportation in Tainan
Tainan has a well-developed, close-knit transportation network, and is one of the main transportation hubs of southern Taiwan. It also has Taiwan’s first comprehensive Smart Transportation Center, with five systems that respectively cover smart traffic control, smart public transportation, smart parking management, smart vehicle sharing, and a smart cloud platform. Tainan City Government is also set upon utilizing the Port of Anping Free Trade Zone Cooperation Promotion Platform to achieve the dual-axis development of “tourism in the north and free trade in the south.” Under this initiative, the free trade zone will provide shipping and logistics operators with a more sustainable operating environment, through realization of the “store in front, factory in back” operating model, and thereby spur industrial development in the zone’s surrounding area.
Smart traffic control
Smart public transportation
Smart parking management
Smart vehicle sharing
Smart cloud platform
                                                  9
Upgrading Smart Living, Creating a Nice Place to Live
]]></page><page Index="12" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 10
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
61
Jiali District
Nanxi District
Nanhua District
•
•
•
•
North-South One-day Living Circle
Tainan to Taipei takes just 100 minutes, Tainan to Taichung 42 minutes, and Tainan to Kaohsiung 15 minutes.
To International Airports
Tainan to Taoyuan International Airport takes about 130 minutes, and to Xiaogang Airport takes about one hour.
To Commercial Ports
Tainan to Anping Harbor takes about 20 minutes on Expressway 86, and Tainan to Kaohsiung Harbor takes about one hour.
To Tainan city center, Shalun branch line connection takes 25 minutes.
High Speed Rail
Bus
Beimen District
Xuejia District
Railway
3
Xinying District
Expressway
Houbi District
86
International Airport
Tainan Airport
The airport is only a 20-minute drive from downtown Tainan.
Commercial Port
Anping Harbor
Upon leaving the port, roads 1-6 and 3-22 connect to Expressways 17 and 86, which swiftly join onto the freeway.
Railway System
Taiwan Railways Administration (TRA)
Train service at 17 stations
Taiwan High Speed Rail (THSR)
Jiangjun District
Qigu District
Liuying District
Guantian District
Liujia District
Annan District
Highway
Yanshui District
1
XiayingDistrict Madou District
84
Shanhua
District
Xinshi Districtx 8
3
84
Baihe District
Dongshan District
Xigang District
Anding District
Danei District Shanshang
Yujing District
Yongkang North District District
Xinhua District
Guanmiao District
Zuozhen District
Longqi District
West Central
Anping District District
South District
East District
Guiren District
86
86 Rende District
Outer Link Roads
Expressways
National Freeways 1, 3 and 8, Expressways 61, 84 and 86.
Inner City Transportation
Bus Service
Green Line (Tainan to Yujing), Blue Line (Tainan to Jiali), Brown Line (Jiali to Sinying), Orange Line (Jiali to Yujing), Yellow Line (Baihe to Madou), and Red Line (Tainan to Guanmiao).
District
]]></page><page Index="13" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Smart City
Taipei City Government taps into smart living upgrades to accelerate the development of innovative economic models such as the platform economy, the experience economy, and the sharing economy, to connect with global technology cores, to build the new generation’s future living environment, and to make Tainan into a development base for Asia-Pacific smart cities.
Smart Electricity Grid
Tainan has achieved outstanding results in pushing initiatives for building a smart electricity grid. Such initiatives include a regional energy-source management plan, forward-looking construction to manage demand by high-voltage consumers, and demonstrating management of demand by low-voltage consumers. In addition, smart meters have been widely installed for both high- and low-voltage consumers, and the development of a disaster-proof micro-grid has been demonstrated, to promote private participation in public infrastructure construction. With the smart grid, renewable-energy power plants, energy storage systems, and energy management centers as the four main areas of focus, strong progress has been made in achieving the goals of regional demonstration, innovation diffusion, smart upgrade, and setting sights on emerging country markets.
Smart Environment
Tainan City Government has set up a Smart Development Center as a response to the era of the Internet of Things (IoT), and launched the Tainan Open Government Platform to engage more citizens in project participation. It has also launched initiatives for establishing high-tech disaster relief, for promoting smart agriculture, for building a smart green-energy and circular-economy residential park in Shalun, and for setting up Taiwan’s sixth national- grade science museum, the National Museum of Science Education and Experiencing the Future. In addition, it has successfully instituted a BOT project for Taiwan’s first smart roadside parking meter system, and has established the Greater Tainan Smart Traffic Center, tapping into IoT value-adding services across agencies, setting up a new cloud platform to integrate traffic information, and combining with surrounding academic institutions, research bodies and industrial parks, to create the next wave of economic and sustainable development.
       Tainan has achieved many “first and only” milestones, successfully presenting the fruitful results of this old capital city’s 4G mobility on the world stage, and gaining international renown.
• Taiwan’s first true 4G smart city.
• Teamed up with Qualcomm for the U.S. corporation’s first Wireless Reach program in Taiwan.
• Taiwan’s first and only city nominated for the 2017 GLOMO Awards, in the Best Use of Mobile for Smart Cities
category.
• Taiwan’s first invitee to the Mobile World Congress in Shanghai, to share its experience of creating a smart city.
• Taiwan’s first city to be featured in a video made by GSMA as a smart city case study.
11
Upgrading Smart Living, Creating a Nice Place to Live
]]></page><page Index="14" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                   HAPTER C3
Twin Engines:
Tainan’s Green Energy Hub and Science Park Clusters
To respond to the dawning era of the green economy, major countries worldwide are actively developing renewable energy sources, and the green energy industry has become a bright light of the global economy. Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City was conceived with the aim of creating a kind of green Silicon Valley in Taiwan, enabling the green energy industry to take root in Tainan, and in conjunction with the Southern Taiwan Science Park, which houses Taiwan’s highest concentration of green buildings, serving as a dual-engine core to drive satellite factory investment in Tainan.
         12 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="15" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City
Green innovation and the circular economy are important drivers of industrial upgrading in Taiwan, and are important subjects of global energy transition. The complementary application of green energy development and the circular economy, and related cross-industry integration, will in the future be key to industrial development. Therefore, Tainan City Government and the central government have joined hands in creating the Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City, the only technopole in Taiwan that has green energy technology as its main focus. Built as a smart eco-city in harmony with nature, and with a human scale of community development, Shalun Science City will form increasingly strong linkages with surrounding industrial park occupants and academic institutions, linking them into a green energy industry eco-chain.
The Science City will have five main occupants: the Joint Research Center for Green Energy Technologies, the Green Energy Technology Demonstration Site, the Greater Tainan Convention and Exhibition Center, the Taiwan CAR Lab autonomous vehicle testing facility, and the Southern Campus of Academia Sinica, occupying a total of 27.47 hectares, and will gradually form external links with research institutions and science parks or industrial parks around it. All of its construction projects will be completed by the end of 2019. Once it is fully up and running, it is expected to create a domestic demand market for green energy, and progressively display Taiwan’s R&D prowess to the world.
       13
 TwinEngines: Tainan’sGreenEnergyHubandScienceParkClusters
]]></page><page Index="16" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[m山
86
凹仔 龜仔廓
南151
The Southern Campus of Academia Sinica
The Southern Campus of Academia Sinica establishes a new research and
六甲
 路
六
三
甲
路
六甲
凱旋路
三
段
一段
中
山
崙一街
街
中 正南路
崙
高
崑
速
鐵路
路
溪
街
爺
上
三
德
上崙
崙
公
中
路
崑崙街
一段
路
南
正
中
高
中山高
街
路二段
安
速
路
路
保
崑崙
段
二
路
中山高 速
南
花園
大潭交流道 11
北武東
南149
武東
刣豬厝 大潭
長榮大學
長榮大學
大潭交流道 11
高公
正
街
速
公
崙
中
段
崑
一
路
正
中
高
速鐵
中山
公
路
德崙
段
速
路
賢
線
文
(
南段)
路
二
一
中
長榮路
段
路
榮
洲
路
洲段
路
中
一
長
縱貫
段
路
二
仁
溪
縱
貫
二
線(
仁
溪
南
二
仁
段
溪
)
中山
路
14
1
後壁厝 三塊厝
Joint Research Center for Green Energy Technologies
This will be the hub of Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City, bridging
together research results, employing an open innovation approach, initiating
development projects, and playing an active role in taking up the results of
research conducted in the center and in the outside academic world, and
transforming them into technologies and products that can be commoditized
田厝
and introduced into global markets.
蔦松腳
南160
仁德系統交流道 330
上崙交流道 10
三甲仔
仁德
The Green Energy Technology Demonstration Site serves mainly to provide a
complete testing and proving ground for advanced energy production systems.
39
competitiven保es安s. I工t w業ill prioritize the promotion of research relating to
development platform that will raise Taiwan’s overall R&D and technological
區 1台糖歸仁
history, nurturing talent and becoming an important Asia-Pacific R&D and
agricultural biotechnology, circular sustainability, and Taiwan’s culture and
innovation incubator.
南農場港 漧分場
台 沙
Green Energy Technology Demonstration Site
It offers the general public a taste of smart green living, showcasing the
中洲
supply of clean energy and smart power dispatch, integrating green energy
technologies into the design of sustainable environments, and narrowing the gap between users and industrial technology, for full mastery of the business opportunities in the development of Taiwan’s green energy industry chain.
大湖
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
中洲
東勢頭
上崙仔
二
層行溪橋
一
中
山
]]></page><page Index="17" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[台南 沙崙
林仔邊
circular economy ideas, distinctive from traditional thinking for such residential parks. Local and foreign business people and research personnel settling in Tainan are welcome to experience the high-tech, comfortable lifestyle offered by these smart homes of the future.
中路
石安
15
86
Greater Tainan Convention and Exhibition Center
Tainan is home to 14 industry clusters, more than anywhere else in Taiwan, on top of a
wealth of cultural, sightseeing and culinary features. The establishment of the Greater
by providing a platform for exchange and interaction, will effectively increase
green buildings and smart technologies, and incorporating
台糖南沙 菕農場Taiwan CAR Lab
台糖沙菕 農場
杞舍
Tainan Convention and Exhibition Center, boosting local industries’ competitiveness
opportunities for contact and connection between domestic and foreign industries, and facilitate cooperation between Tainan enterprises and their international counterparts.
Smart, Green-Energy, Circular-Economy Residential Park
The plans for constructing Shalun Smart Green Energy
Science City included futuristic design for creating a
residential park powered by green energy, featuring
沙崙
深坑
南157
Taiwan has a highly complex traffic environment, while Tainan is home to a strong auto
parts manufacturing industry and high-quality human resources. An autonomous vehicle
industry developed in this traffic and industry situation will have more opportunities and
be more competitive than its counterparts in other countries where autonomous vehicles
are being developed. The Taiwan CAR Lab can support this potential by providing a
site for testing and demonstrating the operation of driverless vehicles, and providing
enterprises with test and demo facilities for their products. It also serves an experiential
and educational purpose for the general public. On the R&D side, Taiwan CAR Lab also
expects to establish technical capabilities for assisting academic and research teams to deepen their work on smart driving technologies, cultivate talent, and develop application services, to complete the layout of the industry’s ecological chain.
大苓
青旗甲
頂厝
土庫
南160
五甲
 南雄路一
TwinEngines: Tainan’sGreenEnergyHubandScienceParkClusters
段
速鐵
高
發
路
高速鐵路
一路
長
榮
路
二
段
溪
仁
二
溪
]]></page><page Index="18" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Southern Taiwan Science Park Industry Clusters
The Southern Taiwan Science Park is one of Taiwan’s three major science-based industrial parks. It occupies an area of 1,043 hectares, and has a higher concentration of green buildings than any other park in Taiwan, with 14 buildings that have been awarded the highest-level diamond green building label. Due to the excellence of its advanced process technology, the park’s IC industry enjoys strong international competitiveness. This particularly enables the park to attract high-tech industries and sci-tech talent, promoting high-tech industrial development, and forming high-tech industry clusters with complete upstream-to-downstream supply chains, thereby strengthening its industries’ international competitiveness. The park’s main industries are:
16 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="19" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Integrated Circuit Industry Cluster
The Southern Taiwan Science Park has a quite complete IC industry cluster. Driven by the wafer foundries of TSMC, UMC and others, the park has attracted a whole chain of related industries from CMP polishing liquid and quartz furnace tube manufacturers to downstream packaging, testing and equipment suppliers. With TSMC continuing to invest in the park, adding the most advanced 3 nm manufacturing process to the 5 nm process of its 12-inch wafer fabrication, it has become a gathering place for the cream of IC industry talent and companies, and the location of the world-leading most advanced manufacturing processes.
Optoelectronics Industry Cluster
The Southern Taiwan Science Park has Taiwan’s most complete cluster for vertical integration of the TFT-LCD industry, with vertical integration of manufacture extending from upstream key components such as glass substrates, liquid crystal materials, touch-sensitive LCD displays, brightness enhancement films and prism sheets, photomasks, and backlight modules, through midstream panels, to downstream LCD TVs.
Precision Machinery Industry Cluster
The development of the park’s precision machinery industry has followed investment in large-scale facilities of the semiconductor and optoelectronics industries, to form an industry-chain cluster effect. Now there are already many domestic and foreign equipment manufacturers in the park, supplying automation, testing and other kinds of equipment, and attracting more investors and precision machinery makers to enter the park.
The Southern Taiwan Science Park’s investment advantages can be divided into three main aspects: tax benefits, single-window administrative services, and abundant R&D resources. The park will continue implementing an array of plans and programs, including the Southern Taiwan Smart Biomedical Industry Cluster Promotion Plan, the Southern Taiwan Smart Manufacturing Industry Cluster Promotion Plan, the Southern Taiwan Science Park Aerospace Key Systems Technology Upgrading Promotion Plan, the Ministry of Science and Technology Science Park Subsidy Program for Industry-Academia Cooperation in R&D Enhancement, and the Science Park Talent Cultivation Subsidy Program, to encourage the park’s manufacturers to collaborate with academic and research institutions, joining together to make Tainan the core engine of southern Taiwan’s industrial development.
      17
                 TwinEngines: Tainan’sGreenEnergyHubandScienceParkClusters
       ]]></page><page Index="20" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                    HAPTER C4
Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
        18 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="21" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[     Amid the competitive strategy of city internationalization and cross-strait economic and trade complementarities, Taiwan is the irreplaceable prime choice for multinationals seeking deployment in Asia. In Tainan, where there are strongly established industries and emerging industries, the city government’s active measures to foster competitive industries, promote the building of complete industry chains, and make the city into Taiwan’s major R&D and global manufacturing industry base, is attracting the attention of international investors. At the same time, the development of benchmark green industrial parks, plus the heightening of land productivity through urban planning, are causing local industries to stay rooted in Tainan.
Tainan’s 14 Bedrock Industries
           Plastics & Rubber Machinery
Plastic Daily Ware
Precision Machinery
Green Energy
Shoemaking
Chinese and Western Medicine Manufacturing
Textiles
Biomedicine
Electric Wire & Cable
Veterinary Drug Manufacturing
Food
Eyewear
Automobile Parts & Components
Culture & Tourism
                                     19
  Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
  ]]></page><page Index="22" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Distinctive Feature Travel and Tourism Industry
At present, there are 22 commercial district organizations established in Tainan, with the purpose of actively creating a superior shopping environment and enhancing the appearance of commercial districts and markets. They are also pursuing the aim of creating a distinctive feature for each commercial district, and shaping an image of Greater Tainan’s commercial districts as places of good food, good fun, and good shopping. Particularly good results have been achieved by an initiative to promote mobile payment to spur business turnover growth in Tainan’s Anping commercial district, which has met with strong approval. All of Tainan’s commercial districts have demonstrated rich creativity and capacity for projecting distinctive features.
  Cultural Knowledge and Digital Content Industries
Fashion Design and Cultural & Creative Industries
Tainan is a stronghold of the textile, garment and shoe industries, and the fashion design industry is one of six major emerging industries that the city government has been vigorously promoting. Moreover, Tainan has Taiwan’s highest concentration of fashion related university and college departments. Through the conduct of brand fashion shows, static exhibitions, and design competitions, providing platforms for display and marketing, the industry’s development is being propelled into transformation from mere production value to much higher brand value, and is gaining a place on the international stage.
Digital Content Industry
Tainan City Government holds monthly interdepartmental meetings to integrate the strengths and resources of industry, government, academia and research bodies, for co-input into developing and promoting the digital content industry. In terms of services, government fee collection, heritage site ticket sales and farmers’ association supermarkets all support mobile payment services, while stores are
being given greater assistance to introduce mobile payment, so that citizens can enjoy the convenience of smart city cashless living. In addition, service enterprises are being encouraged to technologize and internationalize, to boost the digital content industry’s value chain formation and the establishment of cross-industry integrated platform mechanisms, actively spur the digital content industry’s transformation and upgrading, and elevate the international image and international market standing of Tainan’s creativity.
                                                     20 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
  ]]></page><page Index="23" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[High-Value Materials Know-how
Metal Manufacturing Industry Chain: Strongest Development Maturity
Tainan’s metal manufacturing industry is maturely developed with a complete industry chain, and is one of Tainan’s three industries with the highest output value. Distributed predominantly in the Yongkang, Annan and Rende Districts, its 1,924 and more factories constitute 9.23% of all metal manufacturers in Taiwan and 21.5% of all factories in Tainan, the highest percentage among all of Tainan’s industries. Furthermore, with a higher-than-the-national-average level of R&D spending, Tainan’s metal manufacturing industry stands upon an excellent underpinning of R&D potential.
   Auto Parts
There are about 540 auto parts makers in Tainan, one-fifth of all in Taiwan. With a quite complete upstream-to-downstream industry cluster, this agglomeration of factories has the advantages of short delivery times with high levels of mutual trust and specialized division of labor, creating a hard-to-match scale of industry.
Metal Manufacturing Industry
Metal manufacturing is one of Tainan’s traditional manufacturing industries, with strong technical accumulation and resource integration, giving Tainan good prospects of becoming the main base of the metal machinery industry in southern Taiwan. The industry can also receive technical support from the nearby location of the Southern Region Campus of the Industrial Technology Research Institute (ITRI) and the Metal Industries Research and Development Center.
Machinery Industry
Taiwan is the world’s fifth biggest machine tool exporter, and Tainan is home to 8% of Taiwan’s machinery and equipment manufacturing and repair works. Consisting largely of plastics machinery manufacturers, with Taiwan’s largest scale of plastic injection molding machine manufacture, this industry has an opportunity to become southern Taiwan’s metal industry R&D center.
                                    21
Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
]]></page><page Index="24" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Biomedical Technology
Biotech Industry Chain: Best Talent and R&D Links
Besides its traditional strong industries, the biotech industry is an emerging industry that has been a focal target for development in Tainan. Included as one of the six major emerging industries specially targeted for development, great effort has been invested over a number of years to promote biomedical industry cluster development. With the input of substantial R&D energy from major food manufacturers, listed and OTC biotech companies, the Southern Taiwan Science Park’s biomedical device cluster, the Taiwan Biotechnology Industry Alliance, and the biomedicine hub in the ITRI Southern Region Campus, Tainan can already be considered as a substantial biotech city.
  High-end Agriculture
Tainan produces 11.1% of Taiwan’s agricultural output, and is the nation’s top producer of a range of products including orchids, flamingo flowers, star fruit, mangoes, tilapia, white shrimp and milkfish. It is also home to major research units of Academia Sinica and ITRI, which provide academic expertise and talent, plus a number of industry-chain midstream-to- downstream R&D and experimental units, including the World Vegetable Center, the Livestock Research Institute, the Fisheries Research Institute, the Taiwan Sugar Research Institute, and the Tainan District Agricultural Research and Extension Station.
Taiwan’s export of moth orchids has been growing from year to year, with Tainan the main producer of this high-value flower. Taiwan Orchid Plantation in Tainan, occupying an area of 175 hectares, is Taiwan’s largest biotech orchid park. Fully equipped for marketing and dispatching orchids through online and other channels, it is on the point of being made into a
22 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
 world-class orchid industry park.
    ]]></page><page Index="25" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                  Biotechnology
Tainan hosts the three major biotech sub-industries of pharmaceutical manufacturing, applied biotechnology, and medical equipment manufacturing, with more than 470 manufacturers and a complete industry cluster. In addition, the city government has assisted the formation of the Taiwan Biotechnology Industry Alliance, promoting the industry’s development through the launch of a biotech joint testing platform, by annually holding the Tainan Biotechnology and Green Energy Expo, and by setting up a theme pavilion in the BioTaiwan Exhibition and helping industry members participate in overseas exhibitions.
Tainan’s biotech industry has a complete upstream-to-downstream industry chain, from upstream raw materials, R&D, and clinical trials, through midstream manufacturing, testing and verification, to downstream brand marketing, and is already displaying diversified development, with traditional food, beverage and chemical manufacturers crossing into utilizing biotech in their production processes. The industry’s medical equipment sub- field occupies a leading position. Major medical equipment manufacturers have been coming one after another to invest in the Southern Taiwan Science Park, where they have already formed a steadily maturing cluster, transforming and upgrading what was formerly a metal processing cluster into a dental and orthopedic equipment cluster, forming a biomedicine cluster belt from north to south of Taiwan along the high speed rail line, and advancing
23
the development of smart medicine into a model of local industrial transformation.
 Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
   ]]></page><page Index="26" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 24
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
Guiren District
Diverse Industrial Park Development, Pooling Abundant Energy
In addition to the Southern Taiwan Science Park, Tainan has 10 industrial parks developed by the government and 20 developed by the private sector, plus 35 areas designated as industrial zones in the city’s urban planning program. These form the lifelines of industry in southern Taiwan, and are the main economic foundations for connection with the world.
Distribution of
Tainan’s Industrial Parks
Cigu Technology Industrial Park
Guantian Industrial Park
Houbi District
Liuying District
Liujia District
Qigu District
Jiali District
Xigang District
Anding District
Shanhua District
XinshiDistrict
Sinying Industrial Park Southern Taiwan Science Park
Beimen District
Yanshui District
Annan District
Danei District
Shanshang District
Xinhua District
District
Anping Industrial Park
Baihe District
Dongshan District
Nanxi District
Yujing District
Xuejia District Jiangjun District
North District West Central District
Anping District South
District 大大大大大大大
East District
Rende District
Guanmiao District
Longqi District
Xinying District
Xiaying District
Madou District
Guantian District
Yongkang District
Zuozhen
]]></page><page Index="27" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Creating Investment Targets with More Diversity of Choice
佳里區
七股區
七股里
溪南里
義合里
三股里
樹林里
永吉里
義合里
中山路
段
樹林里
路六段
北汕尾三路
曾文溪
城⻄街二段
安明路四段
工業一路
城南路
新生北路
本原街二段
嘉南大圳
淵⻄路
淵⻄路
海佃路三段
本淵路
嘉南大圳
安中路三段
本田路三段
顯宮一街
海佃路二段
中工二路
仁安路
媽祖宮五街
科技三路
曾文溪排水線
路
工業二路
工業五路
科技二路
海環街
本淵寮排水線
媽祖宮路
科技一路
媽祖宮一街
安明路三段
工業五路 工業六路
本田路二段
鹿耳二路
鹽安路
工業七路
竹橋里
海尾寮排水線
工業三路 工業三路
鹽田路
海尾路
本田路二段
工業八路
安明路二段
本田路一段
鹽水溪排水
鹿耳門大道一段
北汕尾一路
北汕尾二路 北汕尾三路
安通路六段
鹿耳門溪
郡安路六段 九份子大道
生態街
宜居路
街
宜居三路
大眾路
永續路
四草大道
大眾二街 大眾六街
安明路一
宜居二路
曾文溪
曾文溪
台南環線高速公路
安中路五段 安中路四段
安定區
Nanhua District
Metal
manufacturing,
basic metals, autos
19
Southern Taiwan Science Park
Established industrial parks (government developed)
Industrial zones in urban plans
General industrial zones件
Electronic components
Auto parts
Chemical material manufacturing 南38 Fabricated metal products
Basic metals
Plastic products manufacturing Machinery
Liouying Technology Industrial Park
Madou Industrial Park
Tree Valley Park
Sinji Industrial Park Yongkang Industrial Park
Yongkang Technology Industrial Park
Tainan Technology Industrial Park
17
17
南36
Tainan’s Major Call-for-Investment and Development Projects
Cigu Technology Industrial Park 十一份
南33
下看坪 股尾
頂義合
南33-1
南38
Size/Hectares
141.34 hectares
Industries
Manufacture of
plastic products
and樹b仔a腳sicmetals 南33
Size/Hectares
495 hectares
Key Industries
海尾寮
南38
鄭仔寮
竹橋國中
Tainan Technology Industrial Park & Taiwan-Japan Industrial Innovation Park
Sinji Industrial Park
永樂溪埔寮
新吉庒
Madou Industrial Park
8
19
溪南寮大排
和平路
海寮堤防
七股區
新吉六路
嘉南大圳 曾文溪分線
安新一路
安新二路
嘉南大圳海寮分線
安新三路
⻄港區
新吉一路
安定區
海中街
學
六塊寮排水線
新吉三路
新吉二路
安順庄大道
安新五路
中工一路
曾文溪排水線
安南區
公學路二段 公學路一段
公學路三段
十二佃路
公
段
171
Size/Hectares
110南.8545 hectares Key Industries
四草
台江碼頭
南寮
北汕尾水 鳥保護區
溪浦寮
埤頭排水線
新生北路
平等路
大同街
中山高速公路
新興街
中正路
自由路
新興街
麻學路
自強街
大同街
興民街
光復路
復興街
仁愛路
南49
industrial zones
嘉南大圳
中華街
佳里區 麻豆區
民族路
麻佳路
建南
176
19甲
Enforcement Rules of the Urban
Planning Act
南3
鷸鴴科濕 地景觀區
鷸鴴科
安南區
保護區
General industrial park
17
Size/Hectares
123.26 hectares
新吉交
2
Key Industries
17
本淵寮
北寮
17甲
沙崙
178
171
新寮
17
麻豆交流道
303
1
Those meeting
公親寮
and auto parts
南131
176
the requirements
of Types A and B
嘉南大圳
新生南路
三民路
中興街
成功街
民
權
自由路
新
173
中崙仔
新吉
176
麻豆區
in the Tainan City
中山高速公路
安吉路三段
興國路
25
]]></page><page Index="28" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                    HAPTER C5
Support and Services for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
    26 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
  ]]></page><page Index="29" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                     Attracting investment has a positive bearing on promoting local prosperity, job creation, and social stability. Tuning into industries’ characteristics and needs, the city government gathers resources from industry, government, academia and research bodies, and provides SMEs and new industries with all kinds of guidance and assistance, to keep on creating a prime investment environment. This not only gives manufacturers ease of mind about investing and going into mass production, but also makes overseas Taiwanese businesses happy to come home to set up factories in Taiwan, with Tainan as the first-choice city for their return to their land of birth.
 27
   Support and Services for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
      ]]></page><page Index="30" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   Easy-to-Apply-for Funding Sources
Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR)
With a view to spurring innovation and entrepreneurship as drivers of industrial upgrading and transformation, the Tainan City Government Economic Development Bureau launched a Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) program to encourage local SMEs to invest in innovation R&D, reduce their R&D risk, and heighten the competitiveness of the city’s industries.
Mainly targeted at six categories of enterprise, namely design & creative enterprises, innovative information and service enterprises, biotech and food enterprises, green energy technology (including environmental protection) enterprises, metal and machinery enterprises, and consumer goods and chemical engineering enterprises, the program was divided into the three stages of preliminary publicity, program execution, and results evaluation. After nearly ten years of implementation, the program has achieved eye-catching results, with subsidies granted to more than 600 enterprises, the establishment of 65 new companies, and the collection of more than 450 patents.
                                                                                                                                                                                                 28 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
  ]]></page><page Index="31" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Credit Guarantee for Special Loans to Young Entrepreneurs and SMEs
    Category 1
Loans up to NT$500,000
• Persons aged 20 to 65, with household registration in Tainan.
• Operating a small business that is exempt from business registration, but has
a tax registration record.
• •
Category 2 Loans up to NT$2 million
Meeting the criteria for recognition as SME.
Companies or ventures established in Tainan and having company or business registration.
• •
•
Category 3 Loans up to NT$5 million
Meeting the criteria for recognition as SME.
Companies or ventures established in Tainan and having company or business registration.
For Tainan’s cultural
& creative, popular fashion, green energy, and biotechnology focal strategic industries.
Category 4 Loans up to NT$1 million
• Persons aged 20 to 45, with household registration in Tainan.
• Having participated in government business startup guidance related courses for
at least 20 hours, or related programs, within the preceding three years.
29
 Support and Services for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
]]></page><page Index="32" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Exempt from public offering
      Lower
Enjoy comprehensive
 funding cost
Go Incubation Board for Startup and Acceleration Firms (GISA)
free counseling
                      Enlarged business scale
To develop small innovative enterprises
Raised recognition
 Go Incubation Board for Startup and Acceleration Firms (GISA)
GISA serves to actively assist enterprises of different sizes to smoothly access funding channels, gradually building a multi-layered differentiated equity market for qualifying enterprises. The Economic Development Bureau has cooperated with Taipei Exchange (TPEx) to promote the establishment of GISA, as a means of assisting small innovative enterprises in Tainan to grow and thrive.
Small innovative enterprises can utilize GISA’s fundraising platform and public joint counseling mechanism to help them establish internal controls, set up accounting systems, and implement corporate governance. This will enhance their prospects for growing and flourishing, and in due course in the future they can obtain emerging stock registration and apply for public listing. GISA thus presents an effective mechanism for expanding the role and contribution of SMEs in Taiwan’s economic development. To date, the city government has recommended 14 enterprises to GISA, of which 7 are in the counseling stage and 7 have already registered. In the future, we will continue to recommend good candidate enterprises, to bolster the foundations of the national economy’s future development, and create a multi-winner scenario.
Small but promising manufacturers that
are discovered and recommended to GISA can be provided with equity fundraising support by GISA, to help them grow and thrive.
30 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
          ]]></page><page Index="33" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Tainan City Self-Government Ordinance for Promoting the Development of Technology and Innovative Industries
This city ordinance provides for various subsidies and other supports for investment projects in the green energy industry, biotech industry, digital technology industry, fashion industry, MICE industry, and other cultural & creative industries, or other technology and innovative industries approved by the competent authority, applicable to the purchase, lease or construction of real estate or certain training and R&D expenditures incidental to the projects, with the purpose of promoting investment that can spur local prosperity, create jobs, and enhance social order. In the future, the city government will continue taking action to create a prime investment environment in Tainan and make it a great place to live in and to move to, and will join hands with manufacturers to create industrial clusters, so as to co-create economic development and increase employment.
    Support and Services for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
   Building Tax and Land Value Tax
Real Estate Rental
Employee Training Costs
Investors can receive a subsidy for the whole amount of these two taxes for the first two years, and half of their amount for the next three years, up to a maximum amount of NT$1.2 million per year, and not exceeding a total of NT$6 million over five years.
Investors can receive a subsidy of 50% of the annual rent as stated in the rental contract, up to a maximum amount of NT$600,000 per year, and not exceeding a total of NT$3 million over five years.
An investor that, because of a capital increase or investment, hires new employees who have household registration in Tainan and meet specified criteria, can receive an annual subsidy of 50% of the new employee training costs, up to a maximum amount of NT$50,000 or NT$100,000 per year, and not exceeding a total of NT$500,000 over five years.
    31
]]></page><page Index="34" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   A Set of Supports for R&D
Six Major Industry Alliances
Tainan has six major industry alliances, whose members engage in inter-enterprise collaboration and resource integration to coordinate and consolidate their market advantages, scale, standards, functions or positions. These alliances offer investors in Tainan a mature and active participatory platform for interactive sharing, from which enterprises can derive mutual complementarities, expansion, and technological exchanges, raising the industries’ competitiveness and creating new prospects of co-prosperity.
     Taiwan Precision Machinery and Mold Strategic Alliance
This alliance guides strategic cooperation among Taiwan’s precision machinery
and mold manufacturers, and integrates resources of industry, government, academia and research bodies, to promote co-marketing and technological innovation, push forward speedy transformation of the industry, and achieve co-prosperity for alliance members.
Taiwan Biotechnology Industry Alliance
This alliance serves to strengthen mechanisms for collaboration between biotech companies and academic and research institutions, and to integrate resources of industry, academia and research bodies, to co-promote and expedite the development of Taiwan’s biotech industry.
Taiwan Green Technology Industry Alliance
This alliance has in recent years been actively involved in the formulation and promotion of draft laws for implementing the government’s green energy policy, in promoting the concepts of energy conservation and carbon reduction, in creating a domestic demand market, and in guiding Taiwan’s green energy industry companies to invest in R&D and strategic cooperation.
Southern Taiwan Textile Research Alliance
In the face of rising globalization, the domestic textile industry has had to cope again with the pressure of intensifying international competition. Members of the industry in southern Taiwan have become acutely aware of the need to accelerate the development of high-value products, prompting the formation of this alliance with the hope of being able to combine industry, government, academic and research sector resources, to propel the industry’s rapid transformation.
Formosa Fashion Industry Alliance
This alliance is mainly geared toward aiding the development of Tainan’s local fashion design industry, formulating strategies for developing and promoting fashion design under the three principles of “integrating creativity and cultural accumulation into products for living needs,” “developing the fashion design industry to match the demands of popular fashion,” and “giving due consideration to cultural accumulation when combining culture and technology.”
Taiwan Auto & Motorcycle R&D and Strategic Alliance
This alliance has the purpose of guiding Taiwan’s auto and motorcycle parts manufacturers to actively invest in R&D and strategic cooperation.
                       32 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="35" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Tourism Factories: A Strong Boost for Local Vitalization
In keeping with the development of Tainan’s tourism industry and the growing global popularity of industrial tourism, our city has launched a range of measures to enhance the content and quality of factory tours and so create a higher-grade tourism environment for the general public. These measures include the selection of excellent tour guides, the introduction of various new technologies (3D printing, AR, green energy elements, and robot guides), the development of diversified products, and the arrangement of training courses. For external integrated marketing, we have utilized small local alliances to arrange eight tour programs that put together visits to tourism factories and nearby tourist attractions. We also pick out high-quality items for showcasing in domestic and overseas travel fairs, and provide matchmaking business promotion, to increase the exposure and visibility of tourism factories.
Tainan has 22 tourism factories, the most in Taiwan, distributed in 15 of its districts. Three of these have been rated as outstanding, and two have been spotlighted internationally. In the future, we will continue to launch activities in concert with central government travel and tourism policies, and will continually guide and assist the transformation of the industry within our city boundaries. We will also help already established tourism factories to upgrade their service quality and product innovation, publicizing and promoting Tainan to the world as a first- choice destination for factory tours.
                                                      33
  Support and Services for Industrial Innovation and Upgrading
                                                                                               ]]></page><page Index="36" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                 HAPTER C6
Combining Public and Private Resources, Reaching out to the World
In order to respond to changes in the global environment, here in Tainan we are instituting a wide array of investment promotion measures, integrating industry, government, academic and research resources, and continuing to build a top-quality and friendly investment environment, to nurture local enterprises. Internally, we are encouraging and assisting Tainan’s traditional industries to keep on transforming themselves, and opening up a new blue ocean of tourism to help keep their business operation sustainable. Externally, we are vigorously promoting local industries, to increase their international visibility, open up international markets, and wrest a win-win situation for Tainan and its enterprises.
           34 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="37" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[      Tainan’s Convention and Exhibition Spotlights Subsidies up to NT$800,000
Besides wooing high-performing businesses here in Taiwan and overseas to invest in Tainan, the city government is strenuously promoting the transformation and upgrading of the city’s industries, and actively assisting business startup, while planning international quality exhibition space, aligning our work with the world, and teaming up with manufacturers to develop overseas markets.
The Greater Tainan Convention and Exhibition Center, set to be situated in the special commercial district of Tainan High Speed Rail Station, will provide a platform for expanding Tainan’s trade with the world, holding business discussion and matchmaking meetings, and maintaining the expansion of investment promotion channels. Moreover, to incentivize the holding of meetings, exhibitions and events in Tainan, as a means of promoting industrial development and international marketing, Tainan City Government has specially drafted regulations providing for subsidies of up to NT$800,000.
Legally established juridical persons, universities, junior colleges, academic research institutions, or civil society organizations, other than public enterprises or political organizations, that hold a convention, exhibition or event in Tainan, may apply for such subsidy, and where a foreign juridical person or organization is the co-host, it must submit the application.
35
        CombiningPublicand PrivateResources, ReachingouttotheWorld
 ]]></page><page Index="38" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Industries Go International, Businesses Expand Domains
Language, funding and distribution channel limitations mean that small and micro enterprises are often unable to independently participate in international exhibitions or negotiations with distributors. To remedy this situation, Tainan City Government’s Economic Development Bureau specially drew up and launched the Global Trade Cooperation and Expansion Program, inviting the counterparts of potential buyers to attend exhibitions and conducting matchmaking for them, plus compiling a catalogue of the products of Tainan’s participating manufacturers, to better introduce them to buyers. In addition, to enable manufacturers to more quickly assimilate into the atmosphere of international exhibitions, the program arranges for senior personnel from companies with strong sales promotion experience to coach them on interacting with potential buyers and touting their products, enabling them to simulate in advance how to benefit most effectively from exhibiting their wares, and clueing them in on local market opportunities. This all helps Tainan’s industries to expand sales opportunities and form international connections, not only enabling them to market their products to the world, but also, by demonstrating Tainan’s outstanding enterprise value, attracting cooperation and investment in Taiwan by major international enterprises, thus effectuating industrial support policy for R&D, production, and international marketing all in one.
Adding to Tainan’s excellent investment conditions and an industrial environment that is highly suitable for advanced technology R&D, the city’s public-private partnership has been fortified, and its copious and flexible innovation power is being projected internationally, creating more profits and profit niches. Choose to invest in Tainan, and you will have the best platform for positioning in the Asia Pacific.
36 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN 大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="39" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  37
CombiningPublicand PrivateResources, ReachingouttotheWorld
]]></page><page Index="40" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Contact Window
Investment and Commerce Section,
Economic Development Bureau, Tainan City Government
Conducts the planning and launch of investment promotion measures, matters relating to the investment environment, the arrangement of investment promotion activities and economic conferences in Taiwan and overseas, and the provision of manufacturing investment services, etc.
Address: No 6, Yonghua Road Section 2, Anping District, Tainan TEL: +886-6-2982810
FAX: +886-6-2982835
Web address: economic.tainan.gov.tw
E-mail: investtainan@mail.tainan.gov.tw
    Tainan City Government Economic Development Bureau
Tainan City
Investment Invitation Service
38 INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大
 ]]></page><page Index="41" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[39
 Investment Related Offices and Contact Information
InvesTaiwan Service Center, MOEA
Department of Investment Services, MOEA
Provides integrated one-stop investment services for investors from Taiwan and overseas, plus solution services for investment project problems and difficulties.
Address: 8F, No. 1, Xiangyang Road, Taipei 10046 Tel: +886-2-2311-2031
E-mail: recruit@moea.gov.tw
Web address: investtaiwan.nat.gov.tw
Assists foreign businesses to invest in Taiwan and domestic businesses to invest overseas. Its remit includes promoting domestic and foreign investment and technical cooperation, guiding and assisting outward investment, compiling introductions to investment opportunities and environments, and attracting talent from overseas.
Tel: 886-2-2389-2111, 886-2-2382-0493
Fax: 886-2-23820497/8
E-mail: dois@moea.gov.tw
Address: 8F, No. 71, Guanqian Road, Taipei 10047 Web address: www.dois.moea.gov.tw
Responsible for screening and approval of investment and technical cooperation in Taiwan by foreign nationals and overseas Chinese, and of outward investment.
Tel: 886-2-3343-5700
E-mail: serve@moeaic.gov.tw
Address: 8F, No. 7, Roosevelt Road Section 1, Taipei 100 Web address: www.moeaic.gov.tw
    Investment Commission, MOEA
 ]]></page><page Index="42" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                          Address
TEL Editor-in-chief Editorial Board Editors Art designs
INVESTING GUIDE TAINAN
大大大大大大大大大
Printed by the Economic Development Bureau, Tainan City Government in November 2019
No. 36, Minjhih Road, Sinying District, Tainan 73001
06-6322231
Guo A-mei
Siao Fu-ren, Wang Jyun-bo, Wu Jian-de Lin Shih-rong, Jhen Yuan-yuan
4 Point Design
]]></page><page Index="43" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="44" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   Economic Development Bureau, Tainan City Government
Investment and Commerce Section
T E L +886-6-2982810 F A X +886-6-2982835 economic.tainan.gov.tw
  ]]></page></pages></Search>